Guide to the Honey Lee Cottrell papers, 1950-2015.
Cottrell, Honey Lee papers
- Series IV. Interviews
  - Interview of Honey Lee Cottrell by Brenda Marston, September 6, 2015
    Description of full recording: On Sunday, September 6, 2015, Honey Lee Cottrell and Brenda Marston spent a few hours looking through Cottrell's files and photographs, which she is sending to be preserved in Cornell's Human Sexuality Collection. Cottrell explained the organization and highlights of the collection. A video camera was left on to record the conversation, which could contain helpful insight to those who later want to use the collection. At the end, Cottrell says "They need to be turned loose. I'm glad we're turning them loose on Cornell, but I'm like, man! You know, who's going to be lining up at Cornell to see these things?"
    An excerpt of the interview can be found here:
    Description of Excerpt: September 6, 2015. Talking about her vision for the first issue of On Our Backs and the psycho-sexual subway map of urban lesbian life she created. Shows an ad for her erotic photography and reflects on the vision for both On Our Backs and Countervision. Highlights of her commentary as we look at the photographs and files she is sending to be preserved in Cornell's Human Sexuality Collection. (Talking with Brenda Marston.) 13:54 minutes.
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Books - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
The Blatant Image: A Magazine of Feminist Photography, no. 2, 1982 ( with 2 images by Honey Lee Cottrell and a note by her on the inside cover. Self-portrait on p. 16 and her portrait of Jeanette Foster on p. 30.)
Gayle, Marilyn What Lesbians Do, 1975 (inscribed and signed by the author and artist Barbary)